{
    "id": "ce2cba9f94024493b85b615b4aba6600",
    "title": "Future tense worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "21212c024e42401ba78ebc92910b00b6",
            "title": "Future Tense Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I …………………. you if you say that word again.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will hit",
                        "would hit"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ..................... you tonight.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will phone",
                        "would phone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I promise I …………………. you tomorrow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will visit",
                        "would visit"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘I’m starved.’ ‘I ……………… you something to eat.’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will get",
                        "would get",
                        "am getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "By next Christmas, we ..................... here for twenty years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will be",
                        "would be",
                        "will have been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They ………………… the roof by Saturday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would finish",
                        "will finish",
                        "will have finished"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ..................... by the time you reach her place.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will leave",
                        "will have left",
                        "would leave"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don’t phone them now – they ………………… lunch.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will have",
                        "will be having",
                        "would be"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is no use phoning – they ………………….. by now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will leave",
                        "will have left",
                        "would leave"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This time tomorrow, I ………………… with my grandchildren.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will play",
                        "will be playing",
                        "would be playing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}